[
    {
        "type": "identification",
        "question": "Instructions (computer programs) that when executed provide desired function and performance",
        "answer": "Software"
    },
    {
        "type": "identification",
        "question": "Software system delivered to a customer",
        "answer": "Software product"
    },
    {
        "type": "identification",
        "question": "Produced by a development organization and sold on the open market to any customer who is able to buy such product",
        "answer": "Generic"
    },
    {
        "type": "identification",
        "question": "commissioned by a particular customer and developed by some contractor to suit the specific needs of the customer",
        "answer": "Customized"
    },
    {
        "type": "identification",
        "question": "An engineering discipline that is concerned with all aspects of software production such that high-quality software is produced in a cost-effective manner",
        "answer": "Software Engineering"
    },


    {
        "type": "true-or-false",
        "question": "Software failures receive a lot more publicity than software engineering success stories",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "type": "true-or-false",
        "question": "In the Waterfall Model, customers need interim releases",
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "type": "true-or-false",
        "question": "There are two types of Evolutionary Development: Exploratory and Throw-away prototyping",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "type": "true-or-false",
        "question": "In Throw-away prototyping, development starts with parts of the system that are understood.",
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "type": "true-or-false",
        "question": "In Formal Development, transformations are correctness-preserving so it is straightforward to show that the program conforms to its specification",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "type": "true-or-false",
        "question": "Formal development does not require specialised skills and training",
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "type": "true-or-false",
        "question": "Reuse-oriented development are Used by developers who know of designs or codes which are similar to that required",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "type": "true-or-false",
        "question": "Incremental model was initially suggested by Mills 1980",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "type": "true-or-false",
        "question": "Incremental model is Most appropriate for systems with strict requirements in terms of reliability and risk management",
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "type": "true-or-false",
        "question": "Package-Based Development Model is Based on the use of commercial-off-the-shelf packages (COTS)",
        "answer": "True"
    },


    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "Process phases are interleaved",
        "options": [
            "Waterfall",
            "Evolutionary",
            "Formal systems development",
            "Reuse-based development"
        ],
        "answer": "Evolutionary"
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "Process phases are distinct and separate",
        "options": [
            "Waterfall",
            "Evolutionary",
            "Formal systems development",
            "Reuse-based development"
        ],
        "answer": "Waterfall"
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "System is assembled from existing components",
        "options": [
            "Waterfall",
            "Evolutionary",
            "Formal systems development",
            "Reuse-based development"
        ],
        "answer": "Reuse-based development"
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "A mathematical system model is formally transformed to an implementation",
        "options": [
            "Waterfall",
            "Evolutionary",
            "Formal systems development",
            "Reuse-based development"
        ],
        "answer": "Formal systems development"
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "Describes a set of clear stages in the development process, and a specific set of deliverables (documents, code, etc) which must be produced during each stage",
        "options": [
            "Waterfall",
            "Evolutionary",
            "Formal systems development",
            "Reuse-based development"
        ],
        "answer": "Waterfall"
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "A variation of the repository model; A shared repository of problems, partial solutions, suggestions and contributed information.",
        "options": [
            "Pipeline",
            "Layered",
            "Repository",
            "Blackboard"
        ],
        "answer": "Blackboard"
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "Consists of a central data store and a set of independent components that access the data store",
        "options": [
            "Pipeline",
            "Layered",
            "Repository",
            "Blackboard"
        ],
        "answer": "Repository"
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "Accomplished by applying a local transformation to the input streams and computing incrementally so output begins before input is consumed",
        "options": [
            "Pipeline",
            "Layered",
            "Repository",
            "Blackboard"
        ],
        "answer": "Pipeline"
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "Organizes a system into layers, each of which provide a set of services",
        "options": [
            "Pipeline",
            "Layered",
            "Repository",
            "Blackboard"
        ],
        "answer": "Layered"
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "Widely used for machine control applications and are typically modeled via finite state machines",
        "options": [
            "Implicit Invocation",
            "Process-control",
            "Client-server",
            "Two-tier"
        ],
        "answer": "Process-control"
    }
]